Data Source	From Supplier	From Product	To Category	To Subcategory
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB missile launcher (Green)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB rocket launcher (Gray)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	Office cube periscope (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - sushi roll	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - hamburger	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - hot dog	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - pizza slice	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - dim sum 10 drive variety pack	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - banana	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - chocolate bar	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - cookie	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - donut	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - shrimp cocktail	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - fortune cookie	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	The Phone Company	USB food flash drive - dessert 10 drive variety pack	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - mind if I join you? (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - mind if I join you? (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - daaaaaa-ta (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - daaaaaa-ta (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - you might be a DBA if (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - you might be a DBA if (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - it depends (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - it depends (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - I will get you in order (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - I will get you in order (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - SELECT caffeine FROM mug (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - SELECT caffeine FROM mug (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - two types of DBAs (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	DBA joke mug - two types of DBAs (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - Oct 31 = Dec 25 (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - Oct 31 = Dec 25 (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - that's a hardware problem (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - that's a hardware problem (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - fun was unexpected at this time (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - fun was unexpected at this time (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - when your hammer is C++ (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - when your hammer is C++ (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - inheritance is the OO way to become wealthy (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - inheritance is the OO way to become wealthy (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	"Developer joke mug - (hip, hip, array) (White)"	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	"Developer joke mug - (hip, hip, array) (Black)"	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - understanding recursion requires understanding recursion (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - understanding recursion requires understanding recursion (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - there are 10 types of people in the world (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - there are 10 types of people in the world (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - a foo walks into a bar (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - a foo walks into a bar (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - this code was generated by a tool (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - this code was generated by a tool (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - old C developers never die (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	Developer joke mug - old C developers never die (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	IT joke mug - keyboard not found … press F1 to continue (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	IT joke mug - keyboard not found … press F1 to continue (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	IT joke mug - that behavior is by design (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	IT joke mug - that behavior is by design (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	IT joke mug - hardware: part of the computer that can be kicked (White)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Graphic Design Institute	IT joke mug - hardware: part of the computer that can be kicked (Black)	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	RC toy sedan car with remote control (Black) 1/50 scale	Games and toys	RC toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	RC toy sedan car with remote control (Red) 1/50 scale	Games and toys	RC toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	RC toy sedan car with remote control (Blue) 1/50 scale	Games and toys	RC toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	RC toy sedan car with remote control (Green) 1/50 scale	Games and toys	RC toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	RC toy sedan car with remote control (Yellow) 1/50 scale	Games and toys	RC toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	RC toy sedan car with remote control (Pink) 1/50 scale	Games and toys	RC toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	RC vintage American toy coupe with remote control (Red) 1/50 scale	Games and toys	RC toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	RC vintage American toy coupe with remote control (Black) 1/50 scale	Games and toys	RC toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	RC big wheel monster truck with remote control (Black) 1/50 scale	Games and toys	RC toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	Ride on toy sedan car (Black) 1/12 scale	Games and toys	Ride on toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	Ride on toy sedan car (Red) 1/12 scale	Games and toys	Ride on toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	Ride on toy sedan car (Blue) 1/12 scale	Games and toys	Ride on toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	Ride on toy sedan car (Green) 1/12 scale	Games and toys	Ride on toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	Ride on toy sedan car (Yellow) 1/12 scale	Games and toys	Ride on toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	Ride on toy sedan car (Pink) 1/12 scale	Games and toys	Ride on toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	Ride on vintage American toy coupe (Red) 1/12 scale	Games and toys	Ride on toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	Ride on vintage American toy coupe (Black) 1/12 scale	Games and toys	Ride on toys
Wide World Importers	Northwind Electric Cars	Ride on big wheel monster truck (Black) 1/12 scale	Games and toys	Ride on toys
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) 3XS	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) XXS	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) XS	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) S	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) M	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) L	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) XXL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) 3XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) 4XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) 5XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) 6XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (White) 7XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) 3XS	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) XXS	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) XS	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) S	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) M	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) L	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) XXL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) 3XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) 4XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) 5XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) 6XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	The Gu red shirt XML tag t-shirt (Black) 7XL	Clothes and shoes	Shirts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Alien officer hoodie (Black) XL	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Alien officer hoodie (Black) XXL	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Alien officer hoodie (Black) 3XL	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Alien officer hoodie (Black) 4XL	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Alien officer hoodie (Black) 5XL	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Superhero action jacket (Blue) 3XS	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Superhero action jacket (Blue) XXS	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Superhero action jacket (Blue) XS	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Superhero action jacket (Blue) S	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Superhero action jacket (Blue) M	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Superhero action jacket (Blue) L	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Superhero action jacket (Blue) XL	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Superhero action jacket (Blue) XXL	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Superhero action jacket (Blue) 3XL	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Superhero action jacket (Blue) 4XL	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Superhero action jacket (Blue) 5XL	Clothes and shoes	Jackets and jumpers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Dinosaur battery-powered slippers (Green) S	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Dinosaur battery-powered slippers (Green) M	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Dinosaur battery-powered slippers (Green) L	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Dinosaur battery-powered slippers (Green) XL	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Ogre battery-powered slippers (Green) S	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Ogre battery-powered slippers (Green) M	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Ogre battery-powered slippers (Green) L	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Ogre battery-powered slippers (Green) XL	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Plush shark slippers (Gray) S	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Plush shark slippers (Gray) M	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Plush shark slippers (Gray) L	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Plush shark slippers (Gray) XL	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Furry gorilla with big eyes slippers (Black) S	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Furry gorilla with big eyes slippers (Black) M	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Furry gorilla with big eyes slippers (Black) L	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Furry gorilla with big eyes slippers (Black) XL	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Animal with big feet slippers (Brown) S	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Animal with big feet slippers (Brown) M	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Animal with big feet slippers (Brown) L	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Animal with big feet slippers (Brown) XL	Clothes and shoes	Slippers
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Furry animal socks (Pink) S	Clothes and shoes	Socks
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Furry animal socks (Pink) M	Clothes and shoes	Socks
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Furry animal socks (Pink) L	Clothes and shoes	Socks
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Furry animal socks (Pink) XL	Clothes and shoes	Socks
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Halloween zombie mask (Light Brown) S	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Halloween zombie mask (Light Brown) M	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Halloween zombie mask (Light Brown) L	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Halloween zombie mask (Light Brown) XL	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Halloween skull mask (Gray) S	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Halloween skull mask (Gray) M	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Halloween skull mask (Gray) L	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	"Fabrikam, Inc."	Halloween skull mask (Gray) XL	Games and toys	Novelty gifts
Wide World Importers	"Contoso, Ltd."	Pack of 12 action figures (variety)	Games and toys	Action figures
Wide World Importers	"Contoso, Ltd."	Pack of 12 action figures (male)	Games and toys	Action figures
Wide World Importers	"Contoso, Ltd."	Pack of 12 action figures (female)	Games and toys	Action figures
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Small sized bubblewrap roll 10m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Medium sized bubblewrap roll 20m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Large sized bubblewrap roll 50m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	10 mm Double sided bubble wrap 10m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	10 mm Double sided bubble wrap 20m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	10 mm Double sided bubble wrap 50m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	20 mm Double sided bubble wrap 10m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	20 mm Double sided bubble wrap 20m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	20 mm Double sided bubble wrap 50m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	32 mm Double sided bubble wrap 10m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	32 mm Double sided bubble wrap 20m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	32 mm Double sided bubble wrap 50m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	10 mm Anti static bubble wrap (Blue) 10m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	10 mm Anti static bubble wrap (Blue) 20m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	10 mm Anti static bubble wrap (Blue) 50m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	20 mm Anti static bubble wrap (Blue) 10m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	20 mm Anti static bubble wrap (Blue) 20m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	20 mm Anti static bubble wrap (Blue) 50m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	32 mm Anti static bubble wrap (Blue) 10m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	32 mm Anti static bubble wrap (Blue) 20m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	32 mm Anti static bubble wrap (Blue) 50m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Bubblewrap dispenser (Black) 1.5m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Bubblewrap dispenser (Blue) 1.5m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Bubblewrap dispenser (Red) 1.5m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Shipping carton (Brown) 413x285x187mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Shipping carton (Brown) 500x310x310mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Shipping carton (Brown) 229x229x229mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Shipping carton (Brown) 279x254x217mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Shipping carton (Brown) 356x229x229mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Shipping carton (Brown) 457x279x279mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Shipping carton (Brown) 480x270x320mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Shipping carton (Brown) 305x305x305mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Shipping carton (Brown) 356x356x279mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Shipping carton (Brown) 457x457x457mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Express post box 5kg (White) 350x280x130mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	3 kg Courier post bag (White) 300x190x95mm	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Clear packaging tape 48mmx75m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Clear packaging tape 48mmx100m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Black and orange fragile despatch tape 48mmx75m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Black and orange fragile despatch tape 48mmx100m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Black and orange glass with care despatch tape 48mmx75m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Black and orange glass with care despatch tape  48mmx100m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Black and orange handle with care despatch tape  48mmx75m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Black and orange handle with care despatch tape  48mmx100m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Black and orange this way up despatch tape 48mmx75m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Black and orange this way up despatch tape  48mmx100m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Black and yellow heavy despatch tape  48mmx75m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Black and yellow heavy despatch tape 48mmx100m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Red and white urgent despatch tape 48mmx75m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Red and white urgent  heavy despatch tape  48mmx100m	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Tape dispenser (Black)	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Tape dispenser (Red)	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Tape dispenser (Blue)	Office supplies	Fasteners
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Permanent marker black 5mm nib (Black) 5mm	Office supplies	Other stationery
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Permanent marker blue 5mm nib (Blue) 5mm	Office supplies	Other stationery
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Permanent marker red 5mm nib (Red) 5mm	Office supplies	Other stationery
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Packing knife with metal insert blade (Yellow) 9mm	Office supplies	Other stationery
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Packing knife with metal insert blade (Yellow) 18mm	Office supplies	Other stationery
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Small 9mm replacement blades 9mm	Office supplies	Other stationery
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Large  replacement blades 18mm	Office supplies	Other stationery
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Air cushion film 200mmx100mm 325m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Air cushion film 200mmx200mm 325m	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Air cushion machine (Blue)	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Void fill 100 L bag (White) 100L	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Void fill 200 L bag (White) 200L	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Void fill 300 L bag (White) 300L	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	"Litware, Inc."	Void fill 400 L bag (White) 400L	Office supplies	Storage
Wide World Importers	A Datum Corporation	Novelty chilli chocolates 250g	Food	Confectionery
Wide World Importers	A Datum Corporation	Novelty chilli chocolates 500g	Food	Confectionery
Wide World Importers	A Datum Corporation	Chocolate beetles 250g	Food	Confectionery
Wide World Importers	A Datum Corporation	Chocolate echidnas 250g	Food	Confectionery
Wide World Importers	A Datum Corporation	Chocolate frogs 250g	Food	Confectionery
Wide World Importers	A Datum Corporation	Chocolate sharks 250g	Food	Confectionery
Wide World Importers	A Datum Corporation	White chocolate snow balls 250g	Food	Confectionery
Wide World Importers	A Datum Corporation	White chocolate moon rocks 250g	Food	Confectionery
